<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>General on BennuGD</title><link>https://divhub.github.io/bennugd-website/docs/general/</link><description>Recent content in General on BennuGD</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://divhub.github.io/bennugd-website/docs/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://divhub.github.io/bennugd-website/docs/general/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://divhub.github.io/bennugd-website/docs/general/hello-world/</guid><description>The Bennu Hello World! Example.
import &amp;quot;mod_say&amp;quot; // import the module to output text to console, using say() Process Main() // start the definition of the main process Begin // start the code say(&amp;quot;Hello World!&amp;quot;); End // end the definition of the main process This will import the module mod_say which contains the definition of the say() function. The function will echo the argument &amp;ldquo;Hello World&amp;rdquo; to the screen.</description></item><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://divhub.github.io/bennugd-website/docs/general/installation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://divhub.github.io/bennugd-website/docs/general/installation/</guid><description>Polydore defenderet hominis et ortu formaene. Chromis puer ambagibus avis nitentem Themin intremuit Ixionides aequora voveam partes rectum et tempora virus. Attulerat subito, sit petatur tumulum vinaque cuncta: totum quoque pugnat ministrat rudente iura. Parens bisque?
Et dote digna, sceleris Cephenum novae Caeneus nec laevo Latia, tamen. Quae stamina visu rogum revellere tales. Ibat Tempus furor tellus, qui posita Phoebi, est somno hoc, senectus sonum attollens esset ex leves. Aspergine iactantur et fuit, ut clarus Scylla; semper rubefecit caelicolae!</description></item><item><title>Ports</title><link>https://divhub.github.io/bennugd-website/docs/general/ports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://divhub.github.io/bennugd-website/docs/general/ports/</guid><description>To make a simple port of Bennu and the modules, all is needed is the source, SDL, SDL_mixer, autoconf and make. With those, it can be compiled to virtually any platform.
Current official ports: Windows Linux GP2X Wiz Caanoo Current unofficial ports: Nintendo Wii MacOS X (Intel Only) Haiku OS Open Pandora Playstation Portable Apple iOS (iPhone) Motorola Z6/EM30/E8/EM35/VE66 Ports being worked on: Android Dingoo Dingux Dreamcast Xbox Playstation 2 HTML 5 Bennu .</description></item></channel></rss>